Soretchimatsuri
Omoeki Rai
Comedy Girls
Shoshoshoshon!
You've got too much sense!
Today we'd like to talk a little bit about some important aspects of being an idol, so please welcome our special guest!
Please come in. Thank you very much.
Once again, our special guest is Mr. Goh Yoshida.
How long have I known Mr. Goh?
I'm not a bad person. I'm not a bad person.
So you've known Mr. Goh since his audition, and you came to see his debut live performance.
Yes, I went to Ikebukuro. How was it? I went to Ikebukuro. How was it?
I left with one word... "It was done right." It was done right.
I've been watching your videos on the latest riffraff, and you've been watching them.
The recent TV series "Calling the Great Persons" is very interesting.
Natsume, Dr. Yoshida, and Tanaka... So today, I'd like to welcome Mr. Goh to the show, and we're going to do a project like this.
Let's think about live goods.
Well, of course, Rough Rough has a variety of goods, so let's take a look at them first.
Here are some towels, tote baggers, T-shirts, and acrylic stands.
So, in short, plain goods, since it's still early in our history.
I think it's a good idea to have some basic goods like this, since we're trying so hard to make it more interesting.
You're right. Do you have any favorites? This one right now... Yes, Fujisaki.
The acrylic stand is so cute!
How about one by one? Just one by one... Is it okay to collect them all together?
When did this start? Acrylic stands didn't exist in the past.
The acrylic stand is a very popular item.
It's also spread by taking them along on a trip.
So goods have changed a lot between then and now? It's totally different. What was the mainstream in the past?
I'm a collector of celebrity goods, so I've been selling them since the Showa period.
Back then, phone cards and cell phone straps were the mainstream.
A strap... a real strap. Do you know "Galaga Kei"? I know. There were straps for Galapagos.
But towels and stuff like that haven't changed? Towels are still the same, but now they've become muffler towels.
It used to be a regular festival towel after festivals, but it became popular to put it around your neck at festivals, and it became a part of idol culture.
And then it was replaced by pressed towels? And the pressed towel at the same time?
Is that right? Have you seen any unusual goods so far?
For example, this is an Ebichu merchandise.
It doesn't look like idol goods.
This is nice!
The T-shirt is from Seishun Coco.
I'm so nostalgic I'm about to cry!
I still use it for everyday things, but there was an idol group called "Passpo" that Natsumi Takenaka was involved with.
Are these PASSPO's goods?
Yes, it is
It's really nice!
Isn't it well-fitted?
It's really good.
The design is good, so I bought it right away, but later I saw a member who bought it and used it for the first time.
It's expensive, but it's so well made that it didn't sell because it was too expensive.
I see.
Is there such a thing as idol goods that are too fashionable?
This is a bit of a problem. It's important to be fashionable in moderation.
Don't be too fashionable.
I think that T-shirt is a little too fashionable.
It's true that this picture is very cool.
I've seen idol geeks in Hello Project.
Hello Project used to mainly produce embarrassing goods.
But at some point, they decided to make it more fashionable.
That was not well received by the otaku.
It was bad, wasn't it?
In short, they wanted to carry the members' names and so on.
I see... so it's really tiny.
It's like, "Well, you can use it for everyday use if it only has the tour title in small letters," or something.
But that's not it.
I want to carry my favorite group or individual.
I see.
Bigger and bigger is better.
It's okay to be stylish, but...
But that's not enough to satisfy the idol otaku in me.
I see.
I see... so you want to say you're pushing for it.
Yes, I have a plan to sell a few acrylic stands.
The point is to reproduce the scene of the song with 10 billion points.
I'm going to recreate the scene from the song "Ten Billion Points" with the choreography of that moment for each member.
If you buy them all, you'll get one for free.
I see... so if you line up four of them side by side, the pose will be complete.
Gather everyone together and reproduce it perfectly.
I see... make a princess pose.
That's right.
I see.
That's amazing.That's amazing.
Ideally, I'd like to reproduce the scene from the music video with Sakuma's act keys next to it.
No, you have to buy all my act keys to get my act keys.
Shut up!
You can't get it if you don't buy it this time...
Well, there are many wonderful things, so I'd like to show you this one.
The members' embarrassing faces will be displayed on the official goods, and we're going to have an Akusta goods championship!
I'm not listening.
I haven't heard.
We've had a bit of a discussion about it.
But today... we're going to have you all try your hand at comedy.
It's simple... like we do all the time.
That's right, and then we'll do a comedy act.
That's what we always do.
It's a song, you know?
And whoever comes up with the funniest answer will be photographed in a cool pose or a cute pose, and we'll make it into an akusta.
And then we'll have another one in the akusta besides the regular version.
But if you lose this time
The member who gives the most boring answer will be punished with a funny face or a funny outfit, and the member with the most boring answer will be put in the axsta with the funny face or the funny outfit.
Well, anyway, there will be a penalty game Akusta.
The members will be asked to submit their answers with the least interesting answer.
For the first time in history, the penalty game will be an Axter.
Here's the subject.
What's the word for the idol T-shirt that's too sharp?
There's a one-line name here on the riffraff.
Yes, that's right.
Goods.
I'm thinking this is another idea for merchandise.
So if it's really good, we might adopt it.
What is the word for the idol T-shirt that is too sharp?
Everyday Guess Edition
But it's kind of amazingly beautiful.
You're such a nerd!
The nerd who wrote "Everyday guess edition
Come on, Saito!
What's the word for an idol T-shirt that's too sharp?
I hate you
I hate you even though you're my favorite T-shirt!
I hate you even though you're my favorite T-shirt.
Come on, Takanashi
Please tell me the words on the idol T-shirts that are too sharp.
Nice to meet you.
That's a good one.
The old Yankee.
Yoshimura
Please tell me the word for the idol T-shirt that's too sharp.
Magic is forbidden
Natsume
Please tell me the words on the idol T-shirts that are too sharp.
Look better!
You don't want someone like that approaching you at a handshake event
The one that says, "Put on a better face.
Hayashi
Please tell me the words on the idol T-shirt that's too pointed.
I've gained weight lately.
I hate it.
Saito
Please tell me the words on the idol T-shirts that are too sharp.
spiky stick
Not a handshake.
I don't like that in general.
I hate that.
Nagamatsu
What's the word for an idol T-shirt that's too sharp?
Great pleasure.
I'm afraid of the first pair, too.
Tell me the words on the idol T-shirt that's too sharp.
shedding skin
That's funny.
I hate it when nerds molt.
You're going to be the first one to molt?
No way!
Come on!
Go for it!
What do you say to an idol T-shirt that's too sharp?
I'll give you some money for food.
It's too heavy.
It's too heavy for the idol.
I'm offering you money for food.
That T-shirt is surprisingly good!That T-shirt is surprisingly nice.
Here's the next subject!
The title of the new Ruff Ruff song that P. Sakuma lost his mind over is...
But he's not lost his mind anymore.
And that picture, too... he made up his mind.
I think it's okay if we go for it, don't you?
If you find a really good subject
I'll write it for Mr. Okura.
Okura-san does a lot of things.
I was wondering if you could do it.
Yes, Saito.
The title of the new Ruff Ruff song that P. Sakuma lost his mind over is...
Waku Waku Mansudan (Exciting Full Traffic Train)
Lost in the blood
What the hell!
Why do you have that word in your head?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Chomatsu
Sakuma P got lost in the blood, and the title of the new song by Ruff Ruff is
Comedy Girls
You're aiming to go overseas, aren't you?
Hayashi
The title of the new song of Rough Rough that Sakuma P lost his mind about is...
Everybody's Idol Sakuma
I'm the main
Sakuma in Sancuba
He's the one who makes fun of me the most
He's the best
That's for sure.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
Why do you guys keep going out like that?
It's not like the other one.
This one was raising all of them.
That's right.
Sakuma P. got confused with the title of Ruff Ruff's new song...
It's funny.
It's a rap song.
That's good.
Interesting yo
Listen to this new song.
Yes, Changmatsu.
Let's go!
The title of the new song by Ruff Ruff that Sakuma P lost his mind over is
Whiteboard and me
I don't know...
Whiteboard and Ore
With this great comedy
I know, right?
Mr. Sakuma
A subject for the mind
That's right.
Write it down.
He said he won't give it to me.
Come on, Fujisaki!
Sakuma P's bloody riff on the title of the new song is...
Shoo, shoo, shoo, shoo...
That's good.
But...
Seriously, Mr. Sakuma, it doesn't seem likely
Shoo-shoo-shoo...
"Shoo-shoo-shoo"?
She's got too much sense for an idol!
Come on, Natsume
Sakuma P's bloody rough new song title is
Daikiri Retirement
Daikiki retire
Quit it!
Daikiri Retire!
It's "Daikiri Retire"!
You've really jumped the gun with Tanaka, the teacher who called you.
You bounced, didn't you?
I heard you did.
Sasaki.
The title of the new song by Ruff Ruff that P. Sakuma lost his mind over is...
Sourechimatsuri.
That guy's funny.
Well then, Sasaki, say it now!
Please listen to this new song called "Soulechimatsuri"!
Please listen to it.Now please listen to this.
This is the first performance.
Soulechimatsuri.
That's great.
Okay, Yoshimura.
The title of Sakuma P's bloody riff on a new song is...
I'll be a comedian starting today
The first one is really bad.
I'm going to be a comedian starting today.
Fujisaki
The title of the new song by Ruff Ruff, which Sakuma P lost his mind over, is...
The Labor of Laughter
He's so cute.
He and he is the most ridiculous
Two of the legs are making fun of him
Two of the legs make the most fun of all
Come on, the best of the bunch got to be Axter.
The one that was the worst...
The one that didn't make it was not there.
It's hard to say no.
It's pretty hard to say no.
I don't think there were many "no's.
It's a little embarrassing.
A little embarrassed.
Then it's decided.
It's decided.
Okay, Mr. Goh.
Please.
Which was the most embarrassing answer?
Natsume.
You're a great comedian!
The most suitable to hold the board.
Well, then, you're the one who wrote "Great Retreat of Great Joy" in calligraphy.
Axter will be on the market.
Calligraphy
Calligraphy for the Great Retreat.
Mr. Sakuma, I still think we should release your goods.
I see.
I think it would sell well... T-shirts with this pose.
The image of this is very strong, isn't it?
That's right.
Mr. Sakuma, I'm not talking about the producer, but the image of this.
This one, right?
It's a bit of a solo image.
You've been making shows for 20 years.
I'm losing to this.
What do you think, Mr. Sakuma?
I want you to buy Ruff Ruff's merchandise first.
That's why I mentioned the extras.
The extras are a bit of a show-off.
That's not what I meant.
I mean, if you spend more than 5,000 yen...
It's a clumsy way of doing things.
That's what I meant by "extravagant".
A song about liking yourself, liking yourself, liking yourself
Let me shout Let me cry
You make me like you like you like you
Remember, it wasn't always so
Ten billion points, ten billion points
Give it to yourself, give it to yourself
I'm here now, that's all that matters
I can't forgive myself for the lies I've told
Well, that's it, that's all for Ruff Ruff's goods over overview. Thank you very much.
Thank you for the rainbow of kindness
It's an idea that only the most ardent can come up with!
It's definitely useful!
Thank you very much for your hard work
Thank you very much
There's someone in front of you.
So when I'm doing the choreography, I feel a little relieved that this dance is right.
Pose? Pose?
Yes, it's really on its own.
Pose
What's this?
You're right.
People in the front row would never have thought of that.
I didn't know such an idea still existed
I don't have that kind of idea.
Thanks for seeing me through to the end today.Thanks for watching all the way through today.
I know you subscribe to my channel.
Oh, good.
You did.
You did? Yay. Yeah, of course you do.
Oh, my God. You did. Wait a minute.
You forgot your handwriting. So subscribe to our channel.
So please subscribe to our channel.